For what you said, I think
the blue burger is just [music][singing].
He doesn't have anything on the screen, like my
laptop [music] I left here.
Jajamon I've ordered Jam
I ordered
[music] red be.  What a beautiful color,
I'll live here.  Charot.
[music] It's
not for you, but it's flattering
that I can't close it, I want to rebump
my wardrobe.  [music] Change everything.
Good morning [music] guys.  I
woke up late today.
Well, I woke up at 7:00 and then
I didn't get up.  I have a
scenario like that.  If I don't
get up right away, I can still continue sleeping
.  But most of the time I get up
.  So no more.  It's 9:00.  I
woke up at 8:30, guys.  Happy tomorrow,
I don't wake up late all the time
as a morning person.
So today's agenda has no plans to go out.
I mean, there's nowhere to go.  Today is a
holiday.
Holidays.  There's no school like that.  We are on leave
today.  We're going out.  We are just home
.  We have no outside.  I mean, I might
go out because I
want to repeat it.  I want to
eat roasted chicken again.  Only here
in Schon.  He's not far away.
I will never forget that chicken.
I've been to Korea several times but this is the
first time I've eaten it.
Your mom will be home in just a few days.  So
I want to eat it again.
I will get back to you.  Your mom is just going to work
.  Let's go down.  Let's buy some
bread from Paris baguette.  I'm hungry.
I'm so quiet that I can barely see a person.
Well, it's a weekday.  Maybe at
school, maybe at the office.  Or just.
Paris baguette is just our neighbor.
Actually, I want to eat something
, so it's udon.  I like that.
Those are the pool bottoms.
Hello.
This is what I want.  Screen safe.  Oh, that.
Your sister said to buy me a dinner
roll.  You guys know the dinner rolls
here are so delicious.  Delicious.
So many drinks.  Sparkling lime soy.   The
packaging is so cute.  It's childish.
His ice drop is social.  Wow!  Red
beans.  Strawberries.  Oh, right?  Different
flavors.  Oh, flower flavor.
Oh, this is vanilla.  It varies.  Melon,
melon.  That's it, downstairs.  Let's try this
red bean.  Hazel and I are alone.  There's
still a macho.  Oh, how fun.  Happy.
Happy.  [sniffing] Ice cream.
They also have pasta.  There you go.  rice.
Nice.
Thank you.   That
's just how it is
.  So I'll just bring
everything.  There is no container.
Miss, can I have this?
'Don't
we?'   Oh,
I left my laptop here.  I
almost forgot about this, guys.  Even if
you leave something behind,
you will definitely get it back.  Nandy is
just there.
So there's no need to buy a lot of
bread, guys, just go downstairs and
there it is freshly baked, it doesn't seem like there's any
need to store it.
Breakfast zoo.  It's actually a branch, right?
Yes, branch.  The branch is bread.
Well, their bread here, their buns, are
delicious.  It seems like there is even no
filling.
Good.  Wow.  Ordered from the kupang.
He is not shy.  What?  Why not be juicy?
Boy, their kimchigan is like that.
Correct soup.
Rice is healthy.  What kind of rice is this
?  Brown rice?  Black rice?   This is
only 3,0001.  Is this true?
Then it's really cold.  What is
it?  Mm.
How delicious.  Fish cake.
Mm.
Delicious, guys.
They like the cold here.
Yes, indeed.  Even if it's cold.  Nice.  There's something like
this, right?
Ban.
Their side dishes are delicious.
Besides, it's more often than not satisfying
.
Mm.
Because the flavor is there, guys.  Usually
their main dishes are bland.
Those that exist are nice.
No,
where can I buy that?
In Wark.
Where is that?
There you go.
Just around the corner.
M is
also my favorite cafe,
I usually pass by it every Sunday morning,
we take a long walk to get there,
about 5m.
5 p.m.
Mm.   It's
just me, I can't do that.
Like every Sunday, we'll buy
something cheap.  Mm.  At the market on
Sunday before I go home. I'll be home on
Sunday. I wonder what happened to grandma. Let's go
there.
Mm.  This can
really be included there.
Mm, because he tastes better with something like that.   It's
wrapped, right?  But I
really don't like the soup.  I hope it's
full.
So far, everything
I've ordered has been like that.
Maybe after ordering, but when you
eat it, it'll be soggy.  Is that right?  It
seems like this is going to be an arm, this kittung
flavor
because it has a
nice taste. Now remember that this is not
what you want,
how come all of them are called kimchi
jig, so I'm confused because it's also in Korean,
guys, so it seems the same to me.
Let's have red bean dessert.  The
packaging is nice.
Win packaging,
my son.
My mother's favorite.   It's already
flavored with
bread beans.  There are only a few beans
you can see, but they are delicious.  And then it
seems like I'm eating a lot of greens.
Mmm.  Nos this.  Oh.  The sweetness is high, right?
Mm.  [clears throat] Then it's
casual
for Koreans.  It seems like
they're not always like this.  No, no.  But
for me, it's okay because it's dessert and it's only
small.
Delicious.
Nice.
So many flavors, my child.
M
has melon, with strawberry.   It's even
sorbet.  Mm.  That's great.  What?
They really put it there like
you're in line.  You're waiting in line at the corner
.  You can look here.
What is that?  I bought it.  I won't
buy it.
Do you guys know that?  There is a psychology
behind the placement of food items
in the grocery store.  Even at the airport, what?  Mm.
Even [sighing] at the airport, guys will make
you walk far.  That feeling
you get at the end when you're thirsty.  You'll see
on your left there's a coffee shop or something with
drinks.  So you can buy it.
After they tell you to walk
a long way down, at the end you'll see a
store
.
Well, that is marketing strategy.
That's right.  Business, huh?  I still have a
bimso there
and I still have Queen Aman.  I'm scared
because when I get home, it'll be gone.
I'll just remember
this.  Just come down and you can buy it.
If you go to SM, would you like
that before you go?  Isn't
traffic just traffic?  The duration.
Your t-shirt is cute.  Where is it from?
Unit clow.  Do you know them Zootopia?
No.  I am beautiful.  This is my first time wearing it,
I haven't used it in a while.
I only bought it because it was next to me because
I liked the many colors,
right?  Or
don't you know the characters?
Not
cute.  That's my favorite.
I'll leave that alone.  Go away, go
That's
actually the cartoon I'm watching.  What do
you mean
where anyone can be anything? That's the
catch or nothing. That's the
only thing that's like,
you can be anyone in
the city.
Wow, guys. I like t-shirts that are
a bit oversized when I wear them, except for the
ones I buy. Guys, they're just right.
So you can see my thinness because that's
my peg in life. I want to get sporty. What's
your trip today? Mm.  I also want to
play a little badminton.  That's it.  Mm.
I'm eating my queen Aman.  This reminds
me of my Davao vlog.  Let's eat
Queen Aman.  Then I said
to a bakery shop that is very popular in
Davao for Queen Aman.  I can only say that this is
not worth it.  Here in Korea,
I always say that it's elevated,
but their Queen Mother is not
elevated.  The one
in Davao is even tastier.  Sweet dessert in Davao.
All their pastries are delicious.
What we ordered there was the Queen Aman
because that's their number one.  And also
the white chocolate almond croissants.
But since it's expensive, I'll still use it.
Tastes like o.
Oh my.  I kind of
want to go back to
Davao, but I want to go back to the countryside.  I like
nature.  My trips are now on hold
.  And suddenly the sun came out.
Guys, it was cloudy earlier, but now the
sun is shining.  Blue skies already.
Life changes so quickly.  Yes.
We're going back to the fifth floor.  Usual
place.  Let's work here.
That's all you guys have.  Your mom will just go to work
.  Okay.
I'm full.  So I have energy now.
Bye guys.  I fell asleep.
I've slept too much but I'm sleepy.
That's me.  The more I sleep,
the more I want to sleep.  I said
I stopped and then suddenly
woke up.  I think it was about 10 minutes.
Then suddenly it got hot, it started getting dark and then it started getting
sunny.  It gets dark and then it gets sunny.  It's hot, guys.
The fragrance has a sun.
Someone is cooking, but it seems like
they're only cooking instant noodles.  The smell of delicious rice porridge
.  Gingery.  I want to
ask.  That's yours.  What do you cook?
Ramin.
Yes.
Spicy.
Yes.  The fragrance of the smell.  Is that an egg?
I'm back.
Wow, he has so many things that look like little
toys.
Your mom is so sweet.  They say you shouldn't
sit for more than 30 minutes or 1
hour.  So you need to walk around,
exercise,
because sitting for long periods of time is not healthy
.  What's your trip?
What haven't I really tried yet?
Facetime.  Nothing.  I just craved
.
This is Jajang Mondon.  I
watched a Korean vlog.  They say Jajang is the
dish to order, especially if
you've just moved here.  This should be your first
meal.  That's what
I told you.  When I came
here,
you said so.
Yes, I [laughter] said that.
Sorry.   I'm
sorry.  By the way, this is my first time
tasting it.  This is just mine.
Mm.
Yes, I can't afford to spend the other one person here
.  Big.
Why did you buy it?  Where are you going?
My house has been washed.  I just took a bath.  Is that
so?  Korean homes are so cute
.  It's like having the strength of a
baby doll.  This is my first time eating this
jajangon,
what do you call it, it's just a pangasinan, jajang, this is
tangsuyok.  Ah, this is
their tangsuyok partner, but the tangsuyok
is made of pork.  Pork with sweet and
sour
pork or chicken
pork?
There are almonds
like mayonnaise, even though mom and I share it
.   This is
too much.
Oh, like this.  You'll still have to mix it.
The power to satisfy is immense.
Hmm.  You're funny, aren't you?
Your cravings are Korean too, huh?
Yes.  You've been craving kimchi jig lately
.  Mm.  That's a good idea, isn't it?  Why are
n't you claving the one below?
That's the one with the
chin.
What sometimes?  Mm.
That's what I was thinking earlier.  I said,
"Can I order while
I'm editing?"  I just thought about the noodles.  What?   It does
n't seem like he's a bad person.  This
might be their recipe, but it has no
aftertaste, guys.  Like the one we have
in the Philippines.  'Are
our Mickeys there doing something?'  Mm.
Yes.  Nothing.   There is a
fungus.  Delicious.
I'm full.
Mm.
It's dinner time.
That's right.  That's dinner.
The morning is the day.  It's 6:00.  It's 5
.  My God.  It's already 6:00.  Because it's only
like 2:00 in the morning.
I am wrong.  I can't finish him off.   It
's like breaded pork with
mayonnaise.  There are almonds.  Or
he's not salty.  It's just dark but it's not
salty.  But he's savory.  Pork is
also an ingredient.
Mmm, that's
delicious.  By the way, guys,
I already have friends.  They also eat and
cook ramen.  While waiting for our
vlog,
let's have breakfast first.  Hazel ordered
something.  He said the noodles were
like velvet, like ramen.
He's already cold because I'm still taking a bath.  Oh.  Yes, indeed.
Hmm.  It looks like chicken noodles.  It looks
delicious.  So let's just heat it up.  And
there is a side dish.
I've already finished the kimchi side dish.  I don't know what this is
.  [sniffing]
Ginger is like garlic.  Let's put it together
.  Oops!  There is a lot.  Don't do it all
because the taste might seem strong.
That's only half.  And then
we heat it.  Your mom is a housewife.
Hazel has a job.  Jun is at
school.  It was just me and
Sandy.  Good girl.  Sandy is so kind.
Golden doodle.  Sandy is very kind.
Actually.  This
dog's behavior is very disciplined
.  If he asks for food sometimes,
just give him one time and he'll be fine.  That he will be a
troublemaker.  It's like he knows he
only has one chance.  Chase is
naughty and won't leave.
He's just making demands.  You know
the noodles here, guys, they're not
really tasty.
That doesn't seem very tasty.
The natural taste is very good, I don't want
to say it's bland, so bland,
but some are bland as long as they have a natural taste.
Then the chickens look like they're
being eaten.  Yes.
Tinola.  Marinade.  Delicious.  The chicken is delicious.   There are
so many chickens.  Four.  One, two,
four large ones with a boiled
egg.
The Korean Japanese style boiled eggs are
the ones they soak in
soy sauce.  Very nice.  Chicken mommy Korean
version.  On this trip, guys,
we ate a lot for the first time and
we went to some places for the first time
too, which is nice, right?  Something new at
least.  We have dessert leftovers.   There are
many more of them, guys.  Hezis isn't really
into it anymore.
He just said
he hasn't ordered anything in a while.
But your mommy, these are always
my cravings.
Let's take supplements first.
I've mixed my supplements
here.  That's it.  This is vitamin E.
We're going to the courier.
We will send and shift the
items.
Used, not actually used.  We'll ship
So that's what Hazel brought because
I bought comforters and then a
bed topper which is actually still missing.
We're trying the cargo.
Hazel said it was quick, like 3 days, but then it got
expensive.  So let's see
how unloved you are.   It
turns out that
his legs are up, basculine.
You're going to get muscular because you're working out,
right?  Then you used to walk to UP.
You don't have a ride.
His bones are big which is
good.  He didn't inherit my
thin bones.  But when I was that age,
my bones were big.  It's just getting thinner
overtime.
Up and up.
Niel brought only three.  I was going to buy
two more because I didn't
get back earlier.  I finished the
vlog.  Wait, I'm out of breath.  Where is the
crossing here?  Oh, those crossings, guys, are
difficult.   What a
pity for the weight he was carrying.  It's
still small.
I have the things I bought from him with me.
We took a detour
because we were going to cross
Myongdong and tried.  We were surprised that there was one
here.  Ah, so you tried the one
in Myongdong, that's where the main one is.
Okay.
The beautiful one is literally in his office.
We should be wise.  It's just that it
's 5:00.  They close at 6.
When we got there, it was a bit awkward.
Just here, closer to Sinton.
But I'm out of breath.
The shortness of breath is severe.
Oh, that.  Oh, Korea post guys.  There you go.
Okay.
So these are the sizes.  One
2 3 4 to small.  Why is he
looking at this?  You don't see
old people.
I said it's so great, why is there a mirror?  Hag said
you can't see it, so you can be careful.
That's great.  Complete.
That's it.  Yes, ours is
for more comfort,
oh well, it's not bad anymore, it's
not crowded anymore,
just wait, wait,
I'm trying to hang the
biggest box first, which is this one
below, 300 ph, is that the price?
I'm just wondering,
wow, you're strong, mommy, you're
strong, you closed it
for what you said.  You're getting stronger,
you're getting lower.  Put it down.  Put that down first
before I put my hand up.
M
One more.  One more thing.  Down.
At this point, it seems like you still want it. After all, the
child is still small.  I thought it was
big.
That's the max for what, plain.
Oh, this is
plain.  Do you want something from the
boat?  Not in 30 days,
fighting will not arrive.
Roro that.
That's why it's so fast
via air.  And maybe it's expensive, what I bought is just like
this, and I'll only pay for it
like this, so you can fix it.  Actually,
maybe there are some taboos that
we know about.   I
guess that's the price,
right?  Pasty.
We are air sourced, air ship or EMS,
so what we did was EMS, didn't we
weigh how many airway bills, oh
yeah, we used EMS, there are a lot of people
sending,
meaning 9 kilos, no
guys, 83, the shipping is Php500, then the
box is Php2,300.
The color blue looks straight ahead, right?
Is the burger okay or not?  Is that okay?   It's
okay.  Then there's a brand on the other side
.
Brand or what?
You
probably know the blue burger,
right guys?  Oh. Oh, blue burger okay.
You know we have two choices.
Nobrand or this is Burger.  What do
you think?
You are not a brand, friend.  I didn't
taste anything.  I haven't
tasted both, but my friend's
favorite is the L brand.
Oh, let's go to L.
So we should try the burgers
here.   There's another
one there, guys.  Burgers, too.
He seems cheap.
The fries look delicious.  The
fries are different.  Egg cheese bulgogi
amazing doubleiko.
You know, this is cheaper than the cheap ones, so this
avocado is on the other hand.  Yes, maybe he can be a
favorite because it's also cheap
.
There's still Mexico.  Wow, so
different.  Oh, there's Japan.  Katsu.  Yes, indeed.
Mexican America.  Yes?  Is there an American
you like?  Do you like Mexico?  Or
Japan.  Or do you want something?  Okay.  So
this is our burger.
How many marketing campaigns?  And pay more?
They are quite cheap.  NDB is amazing.  Then
this is the avocado.  So the
more expensive the avocado, the smaller it is.
Because the picture is so big on fries.
Fries, fries.   Potatoes
really taste like
what Burger King
fries are, to be fair.  Oh, thick.
Potatoes are salty and freshly
cooked.  The NB, the no brand, is
like grocery store stuff to us.  We don't have any
burgers yet.  They're pretty cheap
.  So this burger of theirs is also
their take.
We need to taste the NB first.
You like
that flag fit.
How is
this?  6 4,000 is it not 6,4 not
6,400 with the drink and with the fries
set.  Mm.  But minus the drink, Php,000 is
n't bad.  Or maybe.
This is the one with avocado.
Guys,
this is a double patty.  This is the double
amazing
4,001.  He's not a map,
but of course the patty is frozen.  I mean
guys, what is this patty that isn't
real beef, why do I feel like it's
mixed in?  The taste is different from the real thing
you ground, you really ate
five guys,
oh, I guess the fresh beef is like that,
you're so good.  He's not the one who
seems like ah ready mix,
but they're really selling the
duck to the team,
huh?
This is the one with avocado, guys.
That one
has avocado.
Mmm.
This is the avocado taco.  This is
their Mexican.  Something has an acai flavor.  Okay
.
Mmm.  Mm.
At least they can imitate what
they claim.
Not a burger person.  I want to try it.
I should have said, "Let's just shshay
."   There
should be only one.
Mm.  I'm okay.  One bite.  I told
mommy it was just him.
He said he was just a little bit.
I have two bites.
Then he has a
loser here, is it
beautiful with a
light in a
way?
Now all I have to do is to make use of it. I
know and you know what we could be like. This is
around 4,000. This is beautiful. Did
you measure the medium
I measured?  He said that was too big for
me.  Rose, I didn't measure
the fabric, it's
so
beautiful that I'm stressed out. The
shorts are beautiful. These are also beautiful. Oh, the one
on the other hand is beautiful. Nam is also beautiful, but there are so
many. Yes, I have so many of these
colors. Brown is the beauty of
being brown.
It's giving. It's
giving. It's giving. The fall in what is
beautiful brown? [music] Unique
brown. No.
[music]
[music] This is
beautiful.  It's about to tear,
guys.  Oh, how beautiful.  Or
their other [music], they're for summer because
it's cold.  Oh, how beautiful.
[music] She's so excited to checkout
her clothes.  I haven't even gotten around yet
.  N told me that it was really only one I
got it I just picked up one
what is the size 64 and then size [music]
what is the 70
I honestly don't know
I bought it from Sarah in brown it's not my
type I just bought it because
I needed brown beautiful color beautiful
so it's perfect for you
actually beautiful annoying Miss,
[laughter]
just think I don't have a belly but
I have hips.  No, it
's beautiful.  The detail is so beautiful and it fits
my leg perfectly even though
I'm thin.  The cut is flattering or flattering
that cannot be closed.
Ah, it looks like a
small size.  The pants have a nice cut
.
He said it was okay.  He didn't see
that earlier.  Did he see the
black one?  This is a really nice outfit.
Oh, this one is also just brown.  You know you look
good in a dap if you have that
color.  I have many like that.  This is nice too.
This guys is on sale 50%.  It's just that
he's a gargteriz [musician].  That's a nice one.
The old days were different, better.
This is a bet.  This
confuses me a lot.  Let's try this.   They
say I'm small.  They said I didn't give a damn, I agreed,
sister girl.
This is a shame.  I bet there's
no other size in the other branches.
This one no size other branch.  medium no
finish.
So this one,
this I get
this too.  I got this.  No.
Oh.  He said
he was looking for you that night
.  It's giving B. My
sister likes this gray one.  He doesn't like
all white.  He said oh.  You can see it
in his face.
Then he will find you.  He will give you something else
.  It's cute.  The
problem is my waist area because it's a bit
fat, there's no shape to it.   I feel like I
want to rebump
my wardrobe.
Replace everything.  What is [singing]
capsule wardrobe?  What's that?
I don't know that.  Capsule wardrobe is the
classics that are easy to wear,
he says.  Oh, it's approved.  Approve.  Oh
my god,
what did he say?  I'm not Korean, after all.   This is
Korean attire.
Prize.  So
Korean?  I am Korean.  I will
live here.  Charot.
The fashion is terrible.
This is nice.  Just give it some time, guys.
They're like that in the back.  It's okay.
But you know, guys, they're fun because they're
good at remembering things,
they're good at matching clothes.
They're not the ones who seem to be flattering.
They are serious.  They will.   I'll
get something I'll give you the
thing nice just love it the tammy is
big it's a big tamm he didn't like the suit
with the polo he had earlier what it seems
he was annoyed with he gave it to me he said that
doesn't suit you
he said this is what he saw yes be the back is beautiful
[laughter]
but this is what suits me
Yes but I feel it's also nice to be unique like that
very Korean he said because
I'm small madam's good but
he's not good but then he's not the
ball he's different he seems to be
analyzing meaning yes as
he's doing it t's but he's funny
yes ah
you know he's good he said
I'll get in then I got in
yes try it
just try
[clears throat]
I don't plan on going shopping to be
honest.  I just came in here to
look.  I won't buy
from there.
Okay, let's try.  It is said to be inner and then
I will put it on.
Madam said it looks like a blazer
type.  [coughing]
Wow.  Not my style.  This is not mommy
Heidi.  That's so
Jeny.
Jensen's style is not mine.  I won't type.
Where are you, son?
He's right.  Admit it, he's right.
I don't feel it.
But you shouldn't be tacking him
because I like tacking.
Yes, but usually on the court here, they don't tack like that
.  Just like this.  Yes, that's just
how they are.
Yes, it seems like
there's something [clears throat] about
you,
but it's gone.  Small for me.  No, no, no
.  K. Not anymore.  What size?
I don't know.  There is
medium stock.  Medium.
Mm.  Okay.
I'm buying it because it's so
well-maintained.
[clears throat] The
peg is so summery.  Your mommy's
problem area is this.  No.  I know.  This
[clears throat] is my mother
.  Oh, it's beautiful.  Then this is
just yours.
[laughter]
Why do you use this?  Story time of
our spa experience.
Um, that's not my story time in
Korea.  Yes, I'm back home.
I'm home and the weather is bad.  I feel like I'd rather
stay in Korea.  But let's
continue now.  Yes.  There are so many people
messaging and following up.
Me, it's story time.  Me, maybe
my children will forget.  There are so many
reminders.  Yes.  Oh, that's it.  And there are also many
Australia vlogs waiting for you
.  No me Australia vlogs.  Are there any Australian
vlogs?  Blah blah blah blah.
Your mom uploads them one by one.  First things first, I feel like
it is worth sharing because the experience
is
I don't know what adjectives to
use.  Wonderful, amazing,
outstanding,
exceptional.  I mean, I'm so happy
I tried him.  And speaking of service,
the service level is like this.  So
amazing.
But cameras are not allowed.  So when
I got there, they had a form for
me to fill out.  There are a few
questions you need to answer
so they know what
intensity you want for the massage and scrub
.  So after I filled out a fill up,
I was sent down to an area.
I was dressed.  There is a locker downstairs.
I left my things there.
Then there was something like a weighing skill and then
I entered the room.  That's what
you saw in the vlog.
So the temperature of that entire room is controlled
because that entire room
will get you really wet.  If
you were lying there, a
warm person would really shower you with love.  So
the gesture is nice, right?  It's really everything
they need.  So when I went in
, I said to the girl, "Can you have
my phone? Please,
I'll just tell you a story. They said it's not allowed. Anything with a camera, a
phone is not allowed."  But I said, "Just
one, of course
I gave permission to videotape myself, right?"
Unfortunately, I couldn't include him in the
vlog.  Let's just include it here.
Is it a child?  Then there's hot tea and
the scent is nice, right?  So very relaxing
except for the music.  The entire 2 hours
of treatment were nothing.  Forbidden.  Why?  This is
it.  I'll tell you the story.  First step when
I entered, I took a deep bath for
like 5 minutes, right?  He has ah pinor
in na something
salt kemi like that.  Then there's the aroma.
Finally, there is also.  So after 5 minutes, the
girl who was going to
do it for me came in wearing a robe.  Then I saw
him taking off his robe and
I was like [laughter], "Ah, why are you taking off your robe?"
His attire.  While I was
being scrubbed, while I was being massaged
and all, he was wearing two pies.
Sister girl's two pies are beautiful.  It's black and
matchy and then a bit lace, right?  He beat
me.  Yes.  I feel embarrassed because
mine is cotton, but what's that about it, the
brand is wakol.  Then he moved
me to the bed.  The bed is very
sturdy but can get wet and even if it gets
wet you don't feel like
you're cold or something,
you're uneasy, right?  Very good.  The
feeling is
mutual.  Charot.  It feels good to
start with him from my food,
he's really scrubbing.  Then the scrub is a dry
scrub, right?  So he's using
something.  Then I really see a
lot of chaos coming out.
So scrubbing the whole body is really important.  So
I was laid down, they made me lie down, then they made
me roll over to the other side.
He really is like that.  I really
enjoyed it after the dry body scrub,
of course you have a lot of surprises.
You will be poured with water.  Yes.
Pouring water is also fun.  There is pressure
.  But the water, of course, guys,
of course the water is warm.
The water's warmth is just right for your body and
the room temperature is perfect
too.  So after dry scrubbing,
he put on something that looked like milk.
He will repeat the process.  We're starting from the feet
up again.  And then
I'll fall and then I'll roll side by
side.  He did it again.  Ah, when you're getting a
massage, we know that it
goes through the whole body, but when
he repeats the process, that's what's
delicious.  Because it seems like how should I
say it?  He will be able to firm up since he will do
the process again.  So it's like
you're really being conditioned, not
your body or your system being repaired.  Then after the
milk, there's something like a body
mask and then he'll put a warm
towel on you.  Very relaxing, guys.
The spa there is really on another level.  I don't
think we have that kind of service here
.  Maybe there's something in ch in
changrael.  Because the spots are
like 20,000, 30,000, then there's steaming, I
expect there's a facial
massage, then there's a head massage, hair
massage.  He also put something extra
on my hair that really moisturized
my hair.
She softened and became very beautiful.  I really want
to ask him.  What did you use
on my hair?
My hair looks so beautiful.  All the
materials used by me.  The
collagen oils, the masks, the
milk baths, the facial and
hair products, they're so beautiful as is.
I can't explain.  I wanted to
ask what you used so
I could buy it and
scrub my house myself.  Can you just
imagine how many times he
started from my feet to my head in 410 minutes?  Because
he's repeating himself.  He repeats but with
a different process.  Because the first is a
dry scrub, the second is collagen
oil, the third is milk something,
and then there's the fourth mask.  It's
an absolute pumpering.  That's really the
feeling.  I was assigned to be an attendant, and
her energy was high.  As in,
you know, that force is really strong
.  Your mom is just thin.
[sniffs] Sometimes I tell
him that when I'm in the back
I'm saying it's a little soft.  It's soft because
maybe his price is too high, or
my bones will break.  As a first
timer, of course I was clueless.  I don't
know what the process is, what to
do?  I went there because I wanted
relaxation, some pampering, and knowing
South Korea.  Everything there is of high
standard.  So even though I pay a
lot, I know it's worth my money.  And
true, it's really worth my money.
I'll repeat, okay.  When I come back, I'll do it again
.  But I'm thinking about others, but it's
still the same Korean spot.  When it was finished
, I took a shower and then got dressed
.  Then when I got dressed, that's what
you saw in the vlog, where I was drying my
hair.  I blow dry, I put on makeup
, and then I'm done.  Mm.  So
I called him a cook.  And you guys will see that they have
many different
packages.  So it happened that I took
the highest package because
I wanted 110 minutes of pampering.  But
they have lower ones like 30 minutes, 45
minutes, 1 hour and so on.  It's just that
when I was looking at those, there was a
package that looked like it was just high.  I
mean, just scrubbing it up,
massaging it up and all.  But I said,
why does that seem awkward?  Because
if it's just upper, there's only down.
Then there's something that just seems to be backing off.
So I took the overalls.
Just take a look at the
package you can bet on.  Just make sure
you arrive on time.  Don't be
late so that the
treatment time is not reduced.  Because of course, it's a shame that
the treatment is delicious but you can't
get the maximum time.   Did
you pay for that? I'm so happy
I made him something I would love
doing over and over
budget. Our opponent together is just